sexbot.com 2012-03-15

# 

## Privacy Statement

#### Information Collected

No personal information about our visitors is collected by our site. All information collected is strictly for statistical purposes. This information will not be sold or shared for commercial purposes.

#### Cookies

Our advertiser may place cookies on your computer for tracking purposes. We do not have control over these cookies. You may view their privacy policy for more information.

#### Outgoing Links

Porn Videos contains links to other sites. We recommend that our visitors read the privacy policies provided by these 3rd party sites.

#### Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements to you on our website. These companies (1) use information obtained from your visits to this website and other sites to serve ads to you and (2) place unique third-party cookies on your computer through your browser. Also, we use Web beacons provided by third-party advertising companies to help optimize our advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize your browser when a cookie has been placed on your computer. For more information on the privacy policy and data collection of our third party advertisers, please visit their website and privacy policy here [Betawave Privacy Policy]. Some but not all third party advertising companies provide a mechanism to opt-out of their technology. For more information and to opt out of advertisers that provide an opt-out mechanism, please click here [[networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp]](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

#### Disclaimer

All games provided on Porn Videos come as is with no warranty or guarantee. The games provided are believed to be public domain. If you believe content has been placed on the site without consent, please contact us.

#### Notification of Changes

If our privacy policy changes, the changes will be posted here.

#### Contact

You can send questions, comments, or suggestions using our contact form.
